[{"question": " oh no-no-no, i\u0092m, i\u0092m paddling away!", "answer": "  huh?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " wow! really?! we get all this rusty crap for free?!", "answer": " uh-huh. this and a bunch of bubble wrap. and, some of it is not even popped!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  how desperate am i?", "answer": " oh! good thing chandler\u0092s not here, he always wins at this game.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " i just told my mom i\u0092d cater a party for her.", "answer": " how come?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " because i need the money, and i thought that it\u0092d be a great way to get rid of that last little schmidgen of self-respect.", "answer": " come on, i think this is a good thing. i don\u0092t think mom would\u0092ve hired you if she didn\u0092t think you were good at what you do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  hey! umm, do you guys have any juice?", "answer": " just pickle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey uh, rach, funny story. i ah, bumped into joanna on the street yesterday.", "answer": " my boss, joanna? wow, that must\u0092ve been awkward.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " well, no, actually she uh, asked me if i wanted to get a drink.", "answer": "  you ah, you didn\u0092t say \u0091yes\u0092 to that did you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  no. no!", "answer": "  hello, rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " well, not at first.", "answer": " what is she doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i don\u0092t understand! last time you went out with her you said she was a \u0091big, dull dud.\u0092", "answer": " well, i think i judged her too quickly, and this time we were able to take the relationship to the next level.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " well, last time i almost got fired. you must end it, you must end it now!", "answer": " oh, come on! it\u0092s not like this is an everyday occurrence for me! i mean usually i\u0092m pretty much just in there by myself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " chandler!!  promise me, you will end", "answer": " okay, i promise, i\u0092ll end it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " i hope you know what i\u0092m giving up for ya, because she\u0092s not just the boss in your office, if you know what i mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  how\u0092s the hired help?", "answer": " doing great, the quiches are coming along.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what\u0092s this? blue nail polish?", "answer": " yeah, i thought it was cute.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " ahh, that\u0092s what your grandmother\u0092s hands looked like when we found her.", "answer": " let me ask you a question.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hmm.", "answer": " why did you hire me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  oh my god! did you hear that? she hired me because she thinks i\u0092m good.", "answer": " okay, i didn\u0092t hear that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh yeah, she didn\u0092t hire me out of pity, it wasn\u0092t so she could pick on me in front of her friends, she actually thinks i\u0092m good.", "answer": " wow! and hey, it\u0092s cool if you\u0092re a lesbian!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": "  good afternoon, are you the decision maker of the house?", "answer": " uhhhh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " do you ah, currently own a set of encyclopedias?", "answer": " no! no. but ah, try the classifieds, people sell everything in there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": "  excuse me, i\u0092m sorry, you haven\u0092t said anything for about two and a half minutes, are you at all interested?", "answer": " yeah-well-yeah! yeah-oh-yeah. come on in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " that\u0092s weird.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " your nails.", "answer": " oh, i know, i never wear fake ones. i just did it so my mom wouldn\u0092t give me grief about me biting them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh, no, i meant that it\u0092s weird that you only have nine now.", "answer": "  oh my god. wait a minute, i had them put\u009a  oh my god! it\u0092s in the quiche! oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, don\u0092t panic. i\u0092m gonna go to the store, i\u0092m gonna get you another set of nails, no one\u0092s gonna know, and you\u0092re gonna look great.  oh! oh, it\u0092s \u0091cause they\u0092re gonna eat\u0097that\u0092s the problem.", "answer": "   honey, don\u0092t bite your nails.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " okay ah, please don\u0092t freak out. umm, but ah, there\u0092s a blue fingernail in one of the quiche cups, and there\u0092s no way to know which one.", "answer": " and! whoever finds it wins the prize!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  i\u0092m not freaking out.", "answer": " then why are you laughing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " it\u0092s nothing, it\u0092s just that now your father owes me five dollars.", "answer": " what? you bet i\u0092d lose a nail?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " frozen lasagnas?", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " you bet that i\u0092d screw up?! so all that stuff about hiring me because i was good was\u009a", "answer": " no-no-no, that was all true. this was just in case you pulled a monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " you promised dr. weinburg, you\u0092d never use that phrase.", "answer": " oh honey, come on, have a sense of humour, you\u0092ve never been able to laugh at yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  that\u0092s right. my mom doesn\u0092t have any faith in me! oh, that\u0092s hilarious! ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.", "answer": " i don\u0092t get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no, i have faith\u009a", "answer": "  no! you have lasagnas!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " ding!", "answer": " op, the ruined quiches are ready.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " it just doesn\u0092t\u009afeel like we\u0092re breaking up.", "answer": " no, we are. i\u0092m sad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " okay. (they start kissing again, but are interrupted by the phone.", "answer": "  yes.  uh, can\u0092t you wait until tomorrow?  all right.  unbelievable!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " no, no, that was my boss. i have to go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " i\u0092m getting dressed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " when i walk outside naked people throw garbage at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " wait. i wanna show you something.", "answer": " what is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " just a little gag gift somebody gave me.  put your hands together.", "answer": " ah-ha, you\u0092re not the boss of me.  yeah, you are!  ooh, saucy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " you are, you\u0092re gonna leave me like this?", "answer": " knowing you\u0092re here, waiting for me i think it\u0092s kinda exciting.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  oh.", "answer": " hi! i brought you back a macaroon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " that\u0092s weird, she locked the door.", "answer": " y\u0092know why? she\u0092s got the christmas bonus list in there. i saw her working on it this morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " okay, swear you won\u0092t tell, but when mark left he gave me a key to joanna\u0092s office. do you wanna see the list?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " hello, joanna\u009a\u009a\u0092s office.", "answer": "  i\u0092m really sorry but i may be a little while longer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " how little?!", "answer": " a couple of hours, i feel awful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " look, this isn\u0092t funny! you get back here right now!", "answer": " i can\u0092t!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " why not?!", "answer": " i\u0092m in my boss\u0092s car!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " uh-oh, tunnel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "   what?!", "answer": "  rachel, could i see you for a moment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay, here\u0092s the situation. the keys to the cuffs are on the back of the door. could you be a doll and grab them and scoot on over and unlock me? and on a totally different subject, that is a lovely pantsuit.", "answer": " you promised you would break up with her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " i did break up with her! she just took it really, really well!", "answer": " and the fact that you were jeopardising my career never entered your mind?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " it did enter my mind! but then something happened that made it, shoot right out.", "answer": " y'know what chandler, you got yourself into those cuffs, you get yourself out of them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " oh, chandler!! all right, this is it!  you never see joanna again!", "answer": " never!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " you never come into this office again!", "answer": " fine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " you give me back my walkman!", "answer": " i\u0097never borrowed your walkman.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, then i lost it. you buy me one!", "answer": " you got it! here we go! come on! this is great!  ahhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " does it hurt?", "answer": " no, i just always see guys doing this when they get handcuffs taken off them.  hello sweet pants!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " wait a minute! what are you gonna tell joanna?", "answer": " about what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " when she sees that you\u0092re gone, she\u0092s gonna know that i let you out, and that i was in here, and i\u0092m gonna get fired!", "answer": " i\u0092ll make something up! i\u0092m good at lying, i actually did borrow your walkman!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " so, here\u0092s somebody interesting, joey. what do you know about van gogh?", "answer": " he cut off his ear.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " and?", "answer": " i\u0092m out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " wow! that\u0092s pretty nice. i thought he cut off his ear \u0091cause he sucked. what else you got in there?", "answer": " let\u0092s see, ahhh\u009a where does the pope live?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " in the woods. no wait-wait, that\u0092s the joke answer.", "answer": " actually its, vatican city. now ahh, what do you know about vulcanised rubber?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " spock\u0092s birth control.", "answer": "  you need these books.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " this used to be your room?  wow! you must\u0092ve been in really good shape as a kid.", "answer": " ohh, i\u0092m such an idiot. i can\u0092t believe i actually thought she could change.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, who cares what your mom thinks? so you pulled a monica.", "answer": " oh good, i\u0092m glad that\u0092s catching on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no but, why does that have to be a bad thing. just change what it means. y'know? go down there and prove your mother wrong. finish the job you were hired to do, and we\u0092ll call that pulling a monica.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay, umm, if a kid gets straight a\u0092s, his parents would say, \"yeah, he pulled a monica.\" y'know? or a fireman saves a baby, and they go, \"yeah i know, he pulled a monica.\" or someone hits a homerun and the announcer says, \"yeah, that one\u0092s outta here.\" though some things don\u0092t change.", "answer": "  all right, i\u0092ll go down there. but, i\u0092m not gonna serve the lasagna. i\u0092m gonna serve something i make.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " chandler! chandler, please, i have to get you locked up back the way you were, i am sooo gonna lose my job, she\u0092s very private about her office. now i know why.", "answer": " hey, look, you\u0092re in trouble either way! okay? if she comes back and sees me locked to this instead of the chair, she\u0092s gonna know you were in here. so you might as well just let me go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what if i clean your bathroom for a month?", "answer": " it still wouldn\u0092t be clean.  all i want is my freedom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " foot rubs for a month!", "answer": " freedom!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " i\u0092ll take all of your photos and put them into photo albums!", "answer": " freedom! i want my freedom! why won\u0092t you here me?!  sophie, help me! help me!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " so, what do you say, joey? you get the whole set of encyclopedias for twelve hundred dollars, which works out to just 50 bucks a book!", "answer": " twelve hundred dollars? you think i have $1200? i\u0092m home in the middle of the day, and i got patio furniture in my living room. i guess there\u0092s a few things you don\u0092t get from book learnin\u0092.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " well ah, what can you swing?", "answer": " how about zero down and zero a month for a long, long time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " you don\u0092t have, anything?", "answer": " you wanna see what i got?  okay? i\u0092ve got a baby tootsie roll, a movie stub, keys, a kleenex, a rock, and an army man. hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " and a 50.  huh, these must be chandler\u0092s pants.", "answer": " for 50 bucks, you can get one book! what will it be? a? b? c?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i ah, will buy and wrap all of your christmas gifts.", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i ah\u009a oh! i\u0092ll squeeze you fresh orange juice every morning!", "answer": " with extra pulp?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  yeah!!", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " d\u0092oh!!  i\u0092ve got it!", "answer": " you don\u0092t have it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " i have so got it. there\u0092s gonna be rumours about this, there\u0092s no way to stop it. sophie knows, monica and phoebe know.", "answer": " how do monica and phoebe know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh, i called them. and when they ask me what i saw, i can be very generous  or very  stingy.", "answer": "  go on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i can make you a legend. i can make you this generation\u0092s milton berle.", "answer": " and milton berle has a\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " well?", "answer": " they\u0092re not even touching the lasagna!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " oh, they love your casserole.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yes!!", "answer": " it\u0092s hard to believe that just a little while ago this was nothing but ingredients.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  well, everyone seems to be enjoying your dish.", "answer": " and you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i thought it was\u009a quite tasty.", "answer": " so if everyone liked it, and you liked it, that would make this a success. which would make you\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  a bitch?", "answer": " well, i was going for wrong, but we can use your word.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " yes, well i was wrong, and i have to say you really impressed me today.", "answer": " wow!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  hello. joey, rachel, and ross: hey!", "answer": "  hello, chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " wh-what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " oh. (she motions for them to come closer, they lean in and she whispers what rachel told her. the guys both lean back laughing.]", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " no he doesn\u0092t!", "answer": "  two hours, that lasted!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " so did you break up with joanna?", "answer": " i think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " well, it\u0092s good thing you got out when you did, before she blew up like that vesuvius.", "answer": " the volcano?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " yeah. and speaking of volcanoes, man are they a violent igneous rock formation.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " oh yeah, lava spewing, hot ash, of course some are dormant.", "answer": " why are you talking about volcanoes all of the sudden?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " well, we can talk about something else. what do you want to talk about? vivisection? the vasdeferens? the vietnam war?", "answer": " oh! did anybody see that-that documentary on the korean war?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " oh, yeah. yeah.", "answer": " oh god, korea is such a beautiful country.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " with such a sad history.", "answer": " could there be more kims?  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": "  who\u0092s out there?", "answer": " it\u0092s me! good morning!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " rachel, could you come in here for a moment, please?", "answer": " yeah, sure. umm, they didn\u0092t have poppy seed bagels, so i\u009a  oh my word!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i seem to have had a slight office mishap. could you please get the key off the back of the door for me.", "answer": " oh, yeah! yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " you tell your friend chandler that we\u0092re definately broken up this time.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep3.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}]